KAMEN CHARAKLIEV

Sofia Bulgaria · +359889840972

Email :Komboone@gmail.com / LinkedIn Profile :kamen-charakliev-296bbaa8 Whats app : Komboone / Facebook :Kamen Charakliev

Certified Industrial Rope Access Technician with 15+ years of experience in a various activities.

Fully qualified, with a good amount of experience on the ropes and good work ethic.

Always trying to get the job done, in the highest standart and safest way possible.

Responsible and hardworking individual providing safety and quality work with minimum supervision, maintaining zero incidents.

Dedicated to continues improvement and result orientated.

Given the high-risk nature of the work, industrial worker who can't afford to be anything but professional at all times

EXPERIENCE

03\2024 POWERPLANT BOBOW DOL

Chimney inspection and restoration. Cleaning and repairing on the damaged spots inside the. Chimney ,mill scale cleaning, grinding and coated few layers of epoxy paint .Confined space entry with full face mask.

11\17-2023 INFRASTRUCTURE ELEMENTS"-CYPRUS LIMMASOLL

Telecom towers assembly, Installation. Refurbishment of telecom towers, Installation of telecom equipment. Touch up of Radio tower on SBA territories.

08\09-2023 INFRASTRUCTURE ELEMENTS"-CYPRUS LIMMASOLL

Installation of nylon and mesh beneath the working area to capture debris
Installation and inspection of working ropes as per submitted methodology (rope access)
Removal of old Fall Arrest System. Replacement of old bolts with new bolts type TCB
Water blasting and cleaning and brush cleaning—Water jet at 1000 BARs
Painting of all tower with 3 layers of epoxy paint (c5m system).

2021-2022"SME WIND"-SOFIA

Construction of a steel framed wind mast, installation and maintenance of wind measuring equipment and cables. Rigging and lifting with rope winch.

2020-2021 "VECTOR CONSTRUCT"-SOFIA

Inspection of rocks, safety & Precaution measures, Controlled Rock Removal, Cleaning of rocks. Dangerous trees removal. Soil nailing and Rock bolting, installation of a safety mesh, rock fall netting and catch fencing.

2015 -2020 SELF-EMPLOYED AT CHARALPIN -

heat insulation, rope rigging, tree cutting jobs, painting jobs, roof top cleaning, window washing, inspection and cleaning of a grain silo.

2012-2014 "SME WIND"-SOFIA

Construction of a steel framed wind mast, installation and maintenance of wind measuring equipment and cables.

05\2010-05\2011 "GEOSTRAT"- SOFIA

Inspection of rocks, safety & Precaution measures, cleaning of rocks, boring and laying safety & protective mesh by rope access. Soil nailing and Rock bolting, rock fall netting and catch fencing.

05\ 2009-09\2009 "SPEKTUR INGENEERENG"-SOFIA

Facade deconstruction, cleaning, water jet blasting, painting and instalment of new tin facade panels .Heat insulation of an old buildings

2007 -2008 "IZOGAL"-VARNA.

Repairs and restoration of facades and installment of heat-insulation systems and painting.

2006-2007 "TELEBUILD-OOD, SOFIA

Industrial and civil constructions, research, contracting and erection of telecommunication facilities, installation and maintenance of telecommunication equipment.

EDUCATION

1995-1999

S.P. KOROLYOV HIGH VOCATIONAL SCHOOL OF DUPNITSA ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING AND ELECTRICAL FURNISHING OF INDUSTRIAL ENTERPRISES HIGH SPECIALIZED EDUCATION: technician and Technologist

IRATA ASSESSMENT L1 -1/43882

international rope access organization

GWO WINDA ID: KC033655BG

Global Wind organization

LEGAL CAPACITY CERTIFICATE-0030450

Hand held chainsaw and brush cutter

2023 - IRATA REASSESSMENT

2023 GWO BST -BASIC SAFETY TRAINING

First aid , Working at heights, Manual handling, Fire awareness

2023 BOSIET- BASIC OFFSHORE SAFETY INDUCTION TRAINING

Sea survival, First aid, Fire awareness, Huet-helicopter under escape technique

2023 INSTITUTE OF METAL SCIENCE EQUIPMENT AND TECHNOLOGY "ACAD.A.BALEVSKI"

THE CENTRE FOR VOCATIONAL TRAINING IN WELDING

Shielded metal arc welding -SMAW Diploma

CURRENTLY STUDYING FOR INDUSTRIAL COATING APLICATOR AND BLASTER. AN AMPP COURCE

The Association for Materials Protection and Performance—the largest global community for corrosion and coatings expertise

SKILLS

- water jet blasting up to 1600 bar experience
- Manual arc welding experience
- Tree cutting sertified with pruning experience
- Industrial painting experience
- IBO and GEW anchoring experience

- Air and hydraulic drillers experience
- Grinding and cutting experience
- Rigging and lifting experience
- Termal /heat insulation experience
- Lift truck experience
- Snowcat operator